It was a boring night
with an empty
honest street.
I have to know the things you really
think of me.
The
lonely times of fickle line emergencies.
>> [music]
>> Like this cliche
antiquated
honesty.
Nothing [music]
new to say.
Nothing new to describe.
Nothing new to say.
Nothing new to hide.
I've said it before.
>> [music]
>> It's easy writing down some
fighting
>> [music]
>> words.
I've said it before.
It's easy writing [music] down
some
fighting
words.
>> [music]
[music]
>> These walls are listening [singing] to
what I say.
These creatures come
to
>> [music]
>> show their
>> [singing]
>> face.
While it's wearing a mask.
You know
that there's a reason
why it's [music] wearing a mask.
While [music] it's wearing a mask.
You know
that there's a reason
>> [music]
>> why it's wearing a mask.
[music]
>> I've tried to close
an open story.
>> [music]
>> You had a good
idea.
>> [music]
>> I know
>> this is an old sad story.
I wonder
how it feels.
>> [music]
>> The waiting
>> for all the territory.
Don't [music] make much sense to me.
I've said [music] it before.
It's easy writing down
some
>> [music]
>> fighting words.
I've [music] said it before.
It's easy writing down [music]
some fighting
words.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I've said it before.
It's easy writing down [singing] some
fighting
words.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey.